photographyblog.com 2018-10-12

# Privacy | Photography Blog

## Privacy

### Privacy Notice

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We respect the EU’s General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) and this policy explains how we collect and treat any information you give us.

To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. You won’t find any complicated legal terms or long passages of unreadable text. We’ve no desire to trick you into agreeing to something you might later regret.

SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?  
When you browse our site, we automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your express permission, we may send you emails about our site and other products. You can withdraw your permission to receive our emails at any time by using the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of every email you receive from us.

SECTION 2 - CONSENT  
How do you get my consent?  
If we ask for your personal information for any reason, like marketing, we will always ask you directly for your expressed consent, and always provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [mark@photographyblog.com](mailto:mark@photographyblog.com)

SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE  
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 4 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES  
Some of our third-party service partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our partners include:

  * Google Analytics (website traffic analysis)  
Provider’s privacy information:  
<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>
  * Disqus (commenting)  
Provider’s privacy information:  
<https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>
  * MediaVine (advertising)  
Provider’s privacy information:  
<https://www.mediavine.com/privacy-policy/>[  
](https://www.mediavine.com/privacy-policy/)Provider's GDPR policy:  
<https://www.mediavine.com/GDPR/>
  * Impact Radius (advertising)  
Provider’s privacy information:  
<https://impact.com/privacy-policy/>

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies (direct links provided above) so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

Links: When you click on links on our site, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

SECTION 5 - SECURITY  
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

SECTION 6 - SERVER LOG DATA  
When you visit our website, data (such as the date and time of your visit, any pages visited, the type and operating system of the web browser you use, as well as your IP address) is temporarily saved to a file.

This so-called server log data is saved for technical reasons in order to provide the website service, and is subsequently required to ensure the security of the system.

The server log data is subsequently used anonymously for statistical purposes and to enhance the quality of our website by the service providers contracted by us.

The server log data is not linked in any way to your personal data or with other sources of personal data.

SECTION 7 - COOKIES  
We use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website, to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

Some of our third-party partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site to the extent appropriate under the relevant regulations. Photography Blog has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party services for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Photography Blog’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

SECTION 8 - TAKING PART IN COMPETITIONS **  
**If you take part in one of our competitions, we use your details in order to hold the competition, in particular also for informing participants of winning, and if applicable for sending a prize.

SECTION 9 - AGE OF CONSENT  
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

SECTION 10 - COPYRIGHT NOTICE  
All the content (brand, images, logos, videos and text) on this website are the property of Photo 360 Ltd (the registered owner of http://www.photographyblog.com), unless otherwise stated, and cannot be reproduced without the express permission of the owners. 

SECTION 11 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our site is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to provide information to you.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION  
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at [mark@photographyblog.com](mailto:mark@photographyblog.com)
